{"SiteHeading":"Data Capability Assessment","TitleHeading":"Your results at a glance","GoToResultsButton":"Go to results","Demographics":{"H1":"Getting started","Body":"In this assessment, we’ll ask about your current data capabilities across six categories. At the end you will receive a high-level overview of your results with the option to see them in even more detail.","BeginText":"To begin, please tell us about your company.","ToolTipHeading":"Getting Started Heading","ToolTipText":"Storage scalability, failover and recovery, performance, security, updates, operational analytics, in-memory OLTP and analytics capabilities, and query optimization.","ButtonText":"Start your assessment","Industries":{"Question":"What is your industry?","SelectedOption":{"id":1,"name":"Agriculture & Mining"},"Options":[{"id":1,"name":"Agriculture & Mining"},{"id":2,"name":"Business Services"},{"id":3,"name":"Chamber of Commerce"},{"id":4,"name":"Computers & Electronics"},{"id":5,"name":"Consumer Services"},{"id":6,"name":"Education"},{"id":7,"name":"Energy & Utilities"},{"id":8,"name":"Financial Services"},{"id":9,"name":"Government"},{"id":10,"name":"Healthcare, Pharmaceuticals, & Biotech"},{"id":11,"name":"Manufacturing"},{"id":12,"name":"Media & Entertainment"},{"id":13,"name":"Membership Organizations"},{"id":14,"name":"Non-profit"},{"id":15,"name":"Real Estate & Facilities"},{"id":16,"name":"Retail"},{"id":17,"name":"Software & Internet"},{"id":18,"name":"Telecommunications"},{"id":19,"name":"Training"},{"id":20,"name":"Transportation & Storage"},{"id":21,"name":"Travel, Recreation, & Leisure"},{"id":22,"name":"Wholesale & Distribution"}]},"CompanySize":{"Question":"What is your company size?","SelectedOption":{"Value":5,"Name":"1-5"},"Options":[{"Value":5,"Name":"1-5"},{"Value":25,"Name":"6-25"},{"Value":100,"Name":"26-100"},{"Value":250,"Name":"101-250"},{"Value":500,"Name":"251-500"},{"Value":2500,"Name":"501-2500"},{"Value":3000,"Name":"2500+"}]},"UsesCloud":{"Question":"Do you use public cloud computing providers, such as Amazon Web Services (AWS) or Microsoft Azure?","Answer":{}}},"Categories":[{"Category":"Operational Databases","CurrentCategory":true,"CategoryToolTip":{"Heading":"What are Operational Databases?","Text":"Storage scalability, failover and recovery, performance, security, updates, operational analytics, in-memory OLTP and analytics capabilities, and query optimization."},"DisplayMap":[[0,1,2,3],[4,5,6,7]],"DisplayMapNoCloud":[[0,1,2,3],[4,5]],"Questions":[{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Is the uptime availability of your OLTP databases five nines or better (meaning 99.999% or about 5 minutes of downtime per year for 24/7 availability)?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"empty","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D2"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Can you scale up your mission-critical OLTP databases using parallel processing?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D3"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Can you elastically scale out your OLTP databases to manage changes in the load of your applications (such as adding or removing servers without service interruption)?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D4"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Have you performance tuned your key mission-critical OLTP databases (for example: adding solid state drives or flash-based storage)?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D5"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Are you using in-memory technologies in your OLTP databases to get faster performance for your mission-critical applications?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D6"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Do you have the ability to always encrypt data at rest and data in motion (meaning your data is encrypted at all times, from database to application)?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D7"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Do you use the public cloud for data backup, recovery, and archiving?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":true,"Cell":"D8"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Do you use public cloud databases or management tools for your customer-facing applications?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":true,"Cell":"D9"}]},{"Category":"Data Warehouse","CurrentCategory":false,"CategoryToolTip":{"Heading":"What is Data Warehouse?","Text":"Data storage, refresh frequency, storage span, ability to perform analytics and modeling, scalability for different types of workloads, and optimization through parallel processing."},"DisplayMap":[[0,1,2],[3,4,5]],"DisplayMapNoCloud":[[0,1,2,3,4]],"Questions":[{"Answer":true,"QuestionText":"Do you aggregate data from different applications and departments across your company in a centralized repository? In other words, do you have an enterprise data warehouse?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"We define an enterprise data warehouse as a single data repository that aggregates data across multiple systems and business functions across the company","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"","Skip":["D10","D11","D12","D13","D14"]},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Have you eliminated the majority of your data marts within individual departments or functions to focus on a centralized data warehouse?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D10"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Does your data warehouse contain all of the data elements you need for business intelligence reporting or analytics?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D11"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Is your data warehouse scalable enough to support all the data you're loading and all of the users accessing it without experiencing performance degradation?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D12"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Is the majority of information in your data warehouse refreshed daily or more often?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D13"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Do you use the public cloud for your enterprise data warehouse?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":true,"Cell":"D14"}],"DisplayMapSkip":[[0,1,2,3,4]]},{"Category":"Data Lake","CurrentCategory":false,"CategoryToolTip":{"Heading":"What is Data Lake?","Text":"Storage of unstructured data and ability to transform the same into structured data to perform analytics."},"DisplayMap":[[0,1,2,3,4]],"DisplayMapNoCloud":[[0,1,2,3]],"Questions":[{"Answer":true,"QuestionText":"Is any of the data that your company stores unstructured?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"Unstructured data does not have a predefined data model. Examples include raw text, server logs, XML files, location data, and sensor readings.","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"","Skip":["D15","D16"]},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Do you collect and store unstructured data (such as images, raw text, log files, and geospatial information) in a central repository within your organization (such as a file server, document management system, blob storage, or data lake)?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D15"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Do you transform unstructured data into structured data for future analysis (for example: clickstream activity analysis, server logs, or sensor data logs)?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D16"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Are you using big data technologies such as Hadoop or Spark as a central repository to store your data (in other words, do you have an enterprise data lake)?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D17"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Do you use the public cloud for distributed big data technologies such as Hadoop or a data lake on the cloud?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":true,"Cell":"D18"}]},{"Category":"Business Intelligence","CurrentCategory":false,"CategoryToolTip":{"Heading":"What is Business Intelligence?","Text":"Enterprise-wide reporting and analytics that deliver business insights."},"DisplayMap":[[0,1,2],[3,4,5]],"DisplayMapNoCloud":[[0,1,2],[3,4,5]],"Questions":[{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Does your company have policies or guidelines related to how data can be used and analyzed?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D19"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Can business users easily access key reports, KPIs, and dashboards on mobile devices?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D20"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Can business users create new interactive visualizations of data on their own to develop potential insights?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D21"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Can business users receive real-time or near real-time alerts or notifications based on the conditions they've defined?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D22"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Can you extract data from different cloud-based or hosted applications (such as Salesforce, Google Analytics, or Workday) and combine it in an automated way with on-premises data to create BI reports?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D23"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Have you deployed business intelligence tools on the cloud or as a software-as-a-service application?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D24"}]},{"Category":"Advanced Analytics","CurrentCategory":false,"CategoryToolTip":{"Heading":"What is Advanced Analytics?","Text":"Predictive analysis and modeling, machine learning, statistical analysis, and root cause analysis that’s used to create “smart” apps and provide data-driven insights."},"DisplayMap":[[0,1,2,3,4]],"DisplayMapNoCloud":[[0,1,2,3]],"Questions":[{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Do you programmatically run root cause analysis on data to identify root causes for customer churn, product issues, and other concerns?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D25"},{"Answer":true,"QuestionText":"Does your company develop predictive models to anticipate customer churn, equipment failures, or other potential issues before they occur?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D26","Skip":["D27","D28"]},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Have you implemented predictive models in your key software systems?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D27"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Do your models prescribe one or more courses of action and show the likely outcome of each decision?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D28"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Do you use the public cloud for advanced analytics, machine learning, and data modeling purposes?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":true,"Cell":"D29"}]},{"Category":"Cloud Infrastructure","CurrentCategory":false,"CategoryToolTip":{"Heading":"What is Cloud Infrastructure?","Text":"Migration of various workloads (including app development, backup, and recovery) to the cloud and delivering services through the cloud."},"DisplayMap":[[0,1,2,3]],"DisplayMapNoCloud":[[0]],"Questions":[{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Have you applied virtualization technologies to the majority of systems in your organization?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":false,"Cell":"D30"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Do you use the public cloud for development and testing of new data solutions?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":true,"Cell":"D31"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Do you use the public cloud for temporary compute-intensive tasks (such as spinning up additional virtual machine instances to complete a particular analysis)?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":true,"Cell":"D32"},{"Answer":false,"QuestionText":"Have you used the public cloud to deploy applications that integrate with databases behind your firewall (meaning have you deployed a hybrid cloud)?","ShowMe":false,"ToolTipText":"","Answered":false,"SkipMe":false,"IsCloud":true,"Cell":"D33"}]}]}